export const jsquestions = [
  {
    question: "What is the result of the expression '5' + 2?",
    optionA: "'52'",
    optionB: "7",
    optionC: "52",
    optionD: "Error",
    answer: "optionA"
  },
  {
    question: "Which method is used to remove the first element from an array in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "pop()",
    optionB: "shift()",
    optionC: "removeFirst()",
    optionD: "splice()",
    answer: "optionB"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'typeof' operator in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "To check the type of a variable",
    optionB: "To declare a new variable",
    optionC: "To create a type definition",
    optionD: "To perform a type conversion",
    answer: "optionA"
  },

  {
    question: "Which event is triggered when a user presses a key on the keyboard in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "onKeyDown",
    optionB: "onKeyPress",
    optionC: "onKeyUp",
    optionD: "onKeyChange",
    answer: "optionC"
  },

  {
    question: "Which operator is used for strict equality in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "===",
    optionB: "==",
    optionC: "!==",
    optionD: "!=",
    answer: "optionA"
  },
  {
    question: "What does the 'JSON' acronym stand for in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "JavaScript Object Notation",
    optionB: "Java Source Object Notation",
    optionC: "JSON Object Naming",
    optionD: "JavaScript Oriented Notation",
    answer: "optionA"
  },
  {
    question: "How can you convert a string to a number in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "parseInt()",
    optionB: "toNumber()",
    optionC: "stringToNumber()",
    optionD: "castToNumber()",
    answer: "optionA"
  },

  {
    question: "In JavaScript, what is the 'document' object used for?",
    optionA: "To access HTML documents",
    optionB: "To manipulate the structure and style of HTML documents",
    optionC: "To create new HTML documents",
    optionD: "To delete HTML documents",
    answer: "optionB"
  },
  {
    question: "Which method is used to round a number down to the nearest integer in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "ceil()",
    optionB: "round()",
    optionC: "floor()",
    optionD: "truncate()",
    answer: "optionC"
  },

  {
    question: "Which keyword is used to prevent a variable from being modified in JavaScript?",
    optionA: "mutable",
    optionB: "readonly",
    optionC: "constant",
    optionD: "immutable",
    answer: "optionC"
  },

];

// Example Usage:
// Access the question: console.log(questions[3].question);
// Access the options for the question: console.log(questions[3].optionA, questions[3].optionB, questions[3].optionC, questions[3].optionD);
// Access the correct answer for the question: console.log(questions[3].answer);
